If he had fallen to his death before me,
لو أنه سقط ميتاً قبلي،
I'd have nightmares forever.
سأظل أعاني من الكوابيس إلى الأبد.
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
Give me your hand.
أعطني يدك.
Xie Xinxu!
شكرا لك، شينكسو!
What a fool.
يا له من أحمق.
You surprised me just now.
لقد فاجأتني للتو.
I didn't expect you
لم أكن أتوقعك
to die together with me willingly.
أن يموتوا معي طواعية.
That was just an accident.
كان ذلك مجرد حادث.
Besides,
بجانب،
I crawled back
زحفت للخلف
because I was worried
لأنني كنت قلقة
that you might haunt me in my dreams.
لعلّك تطاردني في أحلامي.
Get it?
احصل عليه؟
What was that just now?
ما هذا الذي حدث للتو؟
An octopus?
أخطبوط؟
It's so huge.
إنه ضخم للغاية.
It probably mutated after contacting the Affinity B Virus.
من المحتمل أنه طرأ عليه تحوّر بعد ملامسته لفيروس Affinity B.
Affinity Virus can also infect some animals.
يمكن لفيروس أفينيتي أن يصيب بعض الحيوانات أيضاً.
However, the chances are low.
لكن الاحتمالات ضئيلة.
So, the Special Administration Bureau sent Ren
لذلك، أرسل مكتب الإدارة الخاصة رين
on missions
في مهمات
to exterminate mutated animals.
إبادة الحيوانات المتحولة.
Is it because they will go berserk and hurt people?
هل السبب هو أنهم سيصابون بالجنون ويؤذون الناس؟
Did it
هل فعلها؟
go berserk just now?
هل جن جنونك الآن؟
Looking at its condition,
بالنظر إلى حالتها،
it didn't simply go berserk.
لم يخرج عن السيطرة ببساطة.
It feels more
يبدو الأمر أكثر
like someone was manipulating it.
كأن أحدهم كان يتلاعب به.
No way.
مستحيل.
How can humans simply control the actions of animals?
كيف يمكن للبشر ببساطة التحكم في تصرفات الحيوانات؟
Genus didn't just
لم يكتفِ جنس الإنسان
develop inhibitors in the past.
تطوير مثبطات في الماضي.
It also carried out
كما قامت بتنفيذ
other kinds
أنواع أخرى
of experiments in secret.
تجارب سرية.
[Affinity B]
[التقارب ب]
So,
لذا،
is this an animal that has mutated after being infected
هل هذا حيوان طرأ عليه تحوّر بعد إصابته بالعدوى؟
by the Affinity B Virus?
بواسطة فيروس Affinity B؟
Yes.
نعم.
It is the same type of virus inside a Ren.
إنه نفس نوع الفيروس الموجود داخل جهاز Ren.
So,
لذا،
the superiors requested us to study
طلب منا الرؤساء الدراسة
if the virus can be used
إذا كان من الممكن استخدام الفيروس
to establish a connection between them and a Ren's brain.
لإقامة صلة بينها وبين دماغ رين.
The goal
الهدف
is to control them with the Ren's mind.
الهدف هو السيطرة عليهم بعقل الرين.
Was the experiment a success?
هل كانت التجربة ناجحة؟
I'm not sure.
لست متأكداً.
I'm not interested in any experiments unrelated to you.
لست مهتماً بأي تجارب لا علاقة لها بك.
However,
لكن،
I heard they picked a Ren
سمعت أنهم اختاروا رين
called Nan Xing.
يُطلق عليه اسم نان شينغ.
He formed a connection with this animal.
لقد نشأت بينه وبين هذا الحيوان علاقة وثيقة.
So is this octopus controlled by Nan Xing?
هل هذا الأخطبوط تحت سيطرة نان شينغ؟
Oh.
أوه.
Both of you found out.
لقد اكتشفتما الأمر كلاكما.
Mr. Gu,
السيد غو،
it has been so long.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
I'm surprised.
أنا متفاجئ.
You are actually
أنت في الواقع
one of us.
واحد منا.
Do you want to join us?
هل ترغب بالانضمام إلينا؟
Don't act familiar with me.
لا تتصرف معي بألفة.
We aren't close.
لسنا قريبين.
[Gu Yanqing] What do you actually want?
[غو يانكينغ] ماذا تريد حقاً؟
Naturally, it's to get rid of both of you.
بطبيعة الحال، الهدف هو التخلص منكما أنتما الاثنين.
Besides,
بجانب،
my baby is starving.
طفلي يتضور جوعاً.
Also,
أيضًا،
I'm hungry as well.
أنا جائع أيضاً.
Miss,
يفتقد،
why don't you become my Yin?
لماذا لا تصبحين يين خاصتي؟
Then,
ثم،
I can consider
يمكنني أن أفكر
sparing the remaining people.
مع إبقاء الباقين على قيد الحياة.
So,
لذا،
what's your choice?
ما هو اختيارك؟
I get it.
أحصل عليه.
If you can't think of an answer,
إذا لم تستطع التفكير في إجابة،
we'll just have to get rid of
سيتعين علينا التخلص من
the person who asked the question.
الشخص الذي طرح السؤال.
Don't move!
لا تتحرك!
Xie Xinxu.
شيه شينكسو.
As you already know,
كما تعلمون بالفعل،
as soon as I think about it,
بمجرد أن أفكر في الأمر،
my baby will strangle her to death immediately.
سيخنقها طفلي حتى الموت فوراً.
She formed a pact with me.
لقد عقدت معي اتفاقاً.
She is exclusive to me.
هي لي وحدي.
Even if you get her, it's no use.
حتى لو حصلت عليها، فلن يكون ذلك مفيداً.
If you can defeat me,
إذا استطعت هزيمتي،
that means you have high viral load in your blood, right?
هذا يعني أن لديك حمولة فيروسية عالية في دمك، أليس كذلك؟
Why don't you
لماذا لا تفعل ذلك؟
let my baby suck your blood?
هل تسمحين لطفلي بامتصاص دمك؟
Perhaps
ربما
it can become stronger.
يمكن أن يصبح أقوى.
That sounds
هذا يبدو
like a great deal.
صفقة رائعة.
Xie Xinxu!
شكرا لك، شينكسو!
Deal.
اتفاق.
Enough.
كافٍ.
You need a balanced diet.
أنت بحاجة إلى نظام غذائي متوازن.
Don't overeat.
لا تفرط في تناول الطعام.
No.
لا.
This is far from enough.
هذا غير كافٍ على الإطلاق.
Xie Xinxu, you madman.
شيه شينكسو، أيها المجنون.
Are you trying
هل تحاول
to pump my baby full of your virus?
هل تريد أن تحقن طفلي بفيروسك؟
Stop!
قف!
If you keep losing blood, you will die.
إذا استمر فقدان الدم، فسوف تموت.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Right now,
الآن،
I'm going to burst from excitement.
سأنفجر من فرط الحماس.
Do you want to calm me down?
هل تريد أن تهدئني؟
How do I calm...
كيف أهدئ نفسي...
Next time,
المرة التالية،
I want you to calm me in a more intense way.
أريدك أن تهدئني بطريقة أكثر حدة.
We just
لقد قمنا فقط
exchanged saliva.
تبادل اللعاب.
I hope we didn't form a pact.
أتمنى ألا نكون قد أبرمنا اتفاقاً.
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
An official pact
اتفاق رسمي
will never be so dull.
لن يكون الأمر مملاً إلى هذا الحد أبداً.
The virus in the saliva isn't that concentrated...
الفيروس الموجود في اللعاب ليس مركزاً جداً...
Xie Xinxu!
شكرا لك، شينكسو!
There's a way
هناك طريقة
on this platform
على هذه المنصة
that leads to the transport hub.
وهذا يؤدي إلى مركز النقل.
Mr. Ding.
السيد دينغ.
What have you done!
ماذا فعلت؟
Why did you move the crane arm away
لماذا أبعدت ذراع الرافعة؟
before Mr. Gu was here?
قبل أن يكون السيد غو هنا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Nongyu wasn't there either.
لم يكن نونغيو موجوداً هناك أيضاً.
What's that attitude?
ما هذا الموقف؟
The group of Ren almost caught up to the arm.
كادت مجموعة رين أن تلحق بالذراع.
If he hadn't moved it,
لو لم يكن قد نقله،
all of us would have been dead.
كنا جميعاً سنموت.
[Under Maintenance] Moreover, Gu Yanqing and his intern
[قيد الصيانة] علاوة على ذلك، قام غو يانكينغ ومتدربه
might have already...
ربما يكون قد فعل ذلك بالفعل...
- Don't jinx it!
- لا تُفسد الأمر!
If you have time to discuss something that happened,
إذا كان لديك وقت لمناقشة شيء حدث،
why not think of a way to activate this train?
لماذا لا تفكر في طريقة لتشغيل هذا القطار؟
We should escape
يجب أن نهرب
before those Ren catches up.
قبل أن يلحق بهم رين.
Carry him inside the carriage first.
أدخله إلى داخل العربة أولاً.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Mr. Gu is badly hurt.
السيد غو مصاب بجروح بالغة.
How come you are unscathed?
كيف لم تُصب بأذى؟
Enough.
كافٍ.
Thankfully, there are emergency medical supplies here.
لحسن الحظ، توجد هنا إمدادات طبية طارئة.
I need to do a blood transfusion.
أحتاج إلى إجراء عملية نقل دم.
All of you, go out.
اخرجوا جميعاً.
(Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Move.
يتحرك.
[Affinity]
[التقارب]
How are you? Are you hurt?
كيف حالك؟ هل أنت مصاب؟
[Genus Biological Research Lab Station]
[محطة مختبر أبحاث علم الأحياء الجنسي]
[Do not hold doors]
[لا تمسك الأبواب]
How's Mr. Gu?
كيف حال السيد غو؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
He won't die with me around.
لن يموت وأنا بجانبه.
Mr. Ding.
السيد دينغ.
What happened to your face?
ما الذي حدث لوجهك؟
I...
أنا...
I have a toothache.
عندي ألم في الأسنان.
Wait.
انتظر.
Tell everyone
أخبر الجميع
not to disturb Gu's rest in the carriage.
عدم إزعاج راحة غو في العربة.
That includes you.
وهذا يشملك أنت أيضاً.
You, come with me.
تعال معي.
Do you already know that Gu Yanqing is a Ren?
هل تعلم بالفعل أن غو يانكينغ من عائلة رين؟
That kid doesn't know how to respect elders and juniors.
هذا الطفل لا يعرف كيف يحترم الكبار والصغار.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You...
أنت...
Sorry.
آسف.
He is a threat now.
إنه يشكل تهديداً الآن.
He will go berserk without the inhibitors.
سيصاب بالجنون بدون المثبطات.
Thankfully, Li Mo and the rest
لحسن الحظ، لي مو وبقية الفريق
found a way to activate the train.
وجدت طريقة لتشغيل القطار.
To be safe,
لضمان السلامة،
he should be left here.
يجب تركه هنا.
He went berserk to save me and the others.
لقد جن جنونه لإنقاذي أنا والآخرين.
At...
في...
At least...
على الأقل...
We should find an inhibitor before we leave
ينبغي أن نجد مثبطاً قبل أن نغادر
to turn him back to normal, at least.
لإعادته إلى طبيعته، على الأقل.
Inhibitor?
المانع؟
All the inhibitors were taken away by the group of Ren.
تم سحب جميع المثبطات بواسطة مجموعة رين.
Are you thinking about...
هل تفكر في...
I'll search for one with him
سأبحث عن واحد معه
while ensuring his safety.
مع ضمان سلامته.
No.
لا.
I can do it.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك.
I must give it a try.
يجب أن أجرب ذلك.
I'll give you an hour at most.
سأمنحك ساعة واحدة على الأكثر.
After an hour, the train will depart.
سيغادر القطار بعد ساعة.
Gu Yanqing,
قو يانكينج,
you want it, right?
أنت تريده، أليس كذلك؟
I am an Yin.
أنا من نوع الين.
I'm willing to relieve your pain.
أنا على استعداد لتخفيف ألمك.
Mr. Gu,
السيد غو،
since the day I became your assistant,
منذ اليوم الذي أصبحت فيه مساعدك،
I stopped falling for someone else.
توقفت عن الوقوع في حب شخص آخر.
I was worried that I couldn't be with you,
كنت قلقاً من أنني لن أستطيع أن أكون معك،
until I discovered
إلى أن اكتشفت
you are a Ren.
أنت رين.
A Ren and an Yin make a perfect match.
يشكل الرين والين مزيجًا مثاليًا.
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
If you don't form a pact with me today,
إذا لم تعقد معي اتفاقاً اليوم،
I'll tell everyone
سأخبر الجميع
that you are a Ren.
أنك رين.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
everyone will rush here and kill you
سيهرع الجميع إلى هنا ويقتلونك
when you're weak?
عندما تكون ضعيفاً؟
Let go!
اتركه!
Xie...
شيه...
Mr. Gu.
السيد غو.
I hate her smell.
أكره رائحتها.
Shut up.
اسكت.
♪ City lights, hazy lines ♪
أضواء المدينة، خطوط ضبابية ♪
Get her to leave.
اجعلها تغادر.
♪ Accomplices in passion ♪
♪ شركاء في العاطفة ♪
♪ Shared a sweet damnation ♪
♪ شاركنا لعنة حلوة ♪
Mr. Gu
السيد غو
is hot-tempered when he's hurt.
يصبح سريع الغضب عندما يتأذى.
He has gone berserk.
لقد جن جنونه.
No one here can help him
لا أحد هنا يستطيع مساعدته
but me.
لكن أنا.
Are you an Yin too?
هل أنت أيضاً من نوع يين؟
♪ Watch the game ♪
♪ شاهد المباراة ♪
Don't hand me over to her.
لا تسلمني إليها.
♪ Just name ♪
♪ فقط سمِّ ♪
♪ Who should be blamed ♪
♪ من يتحمل اللوم؟ ♪
What a coincidence.
يا لها من مصادفة!
I'm also an Yin.
أنا أيضاً من النوع يين.
Moreover,
علاوة على ذلك،
I already formed a pact with Mr. Gu.
لقد أبرمت اتفاقاً بالفعل مع السيد غو.
Please give us some space
يرجى منحنا بعض المساحة
so that I can calm him down.
حتى أتمكن من تهدئته.
♪ I see inferno, can't get enough ♪
♪ أرى الجحيم، لا أكتفي منه ♪
♪ Burning city, fiery love ♪
♪ مدينة تحترق، حب ملتهب ♪
♪ It's a fervor, not a crush ♪
♪ إنه شغف، وليس مجرد إعجاب ♪
I...
أنا...
Let me check what's going on.
دعني أتحقق مما يجري.
♪ You smell like something strange ♪
♪ رائحتك غريبة ♪
♪ Like wood ♪
♪ مثل الخشب ♪
♪ Like wine ♪
♪ مثل النبيذ ♪
♪ Like the fading rain ♪
♪ مثل المطر المتلاشي ♪
♪ It's not a problem I can fix ♪
♪ إنها ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها ♪
♪ Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy ♪
♪ ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بين يديك ♪